It's small.
ちっちゃいね
Open it.
開いて
Ah, it's narrow.
あー 狭い
It's small.
狭いね
Doesn't it hurt?
痛くない?
How is it here?
ここどう?
It's still no good.
まだダメだよ
It came out great.
すごい出てきたよ
A lot came out.
いっぱい出てきたよ
What is this?
なにこれ?
It's so naughty.
すごいやらしい
It's super delicious.
め ちゃ くちゃ美味しい
amazing.
すごい
It's so erotic.
めちゃめちゃエロい
It feels so good.
めちゃ気持ちいい
I feel terrible.
やばい気持ち
Ochi
おち
Is it delicious?
ん ぽ美味しい?
I can't do it anymore.
もうできない
It seems possible.
できそう
Here,
ここにさ、
Can I put it in this naughty mango?
この やらしいマンゴーに入れていい?
Yeah.
うん
So beautiful.
すごい綺麗
Do you want dick?
チンチン欲しい?
Is it okay to just leave it like this?
このままだけでいいの?
is that so?
そうですか?
Oh, this is terrible.
あ、やばいこれ
That's terrible.
やばいね
I can't move though.
動けないんだけど
copper?
どう?
terrible.
やばい
It feels really good though.
めちゃめちゃ気持ちいいんだけど
Penis?
おちん?
terrible.
やばい
I can't move.
動けない
What should I do?
どうしよう
Wait a minute, that's terrible.
ちょっと待って、やばい
Wait a minute, it's out.
ちょっと待って、出ちゃった
ah.
ああ
terrible.
やばい
Oh, that's amazing.
ああ、すごい
Oh no, wait a minute.
やばい、ちょっと待って
Let's bring it out again.
また出そう
wait a minute.
ちょっと 待って
It flew great.
すごい飛んだ
How far did you go?
どっちまで行った?